<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Plugin>
<Name>msf</Name>
<PluginURL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/scoltzero/msf/main/msf.plg</PluginURL>
<Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/scoltzero/msf/main/packaging/unraid/msf.png</Icon>
<Overview>
A free and open-source, user-facing all-in-one management tool for DNS and proxy (mihomo / sing-box, in development), packaged for Unraid.
msf installs a lightweight Settings control page plus a self-managed local service. The Settings page is only for enabling the rc service, setting the listen host/port, choosing the data directory, viewing status, and opening the separate msf WebUI. The full DNS/proxy management interface runs in that WebUI.
After you complete the in-app setup wizard, msf can run MosDNS (DNS), Mihomo (proxy/TProxy), and the required nftables rules. Online MosDNS/Mihomo/Zashboard core downloads are verified against GitHub Release API asset SHA-256 digests before install; local uploads remain user-supplied files and are not marked as project-verified. Default sample subscriptions/nodes are inert placeholders only. Persistent data lives under /mnt/user/appdata/msf.
Update and remove msf from the Unraid Plugins page (not via the in-app updater).
</Overview>
<Support>https://github.com/scoltzero/msf/issues</Support>
<Project>https://github.com/scoltzero/msf</Project>
<Category>Network:Management Tools:System Plugins:</Category>
<Beta>False</Beta>
<Date>2026-06-15</Date>
<Changes>
### msf 0.3.4
- Improved Linux uninstall behavior: interactive terminals ask whether to remove the data directory, automation must pass `--purge --yes` to delete data, and `--keep-data` explicitly retains it.
- Uninstall now stops Mihomo/MosDNS leftovers using PID files and component binary paths under the data directory, with stronger protection against broad purge paths.
- Docker, Unraid, and fnOS FPK installs are now blocked from the Linux tarball/systemd uninstall and service install/uninstall paths.
- Improved the default Mihomo config with sniffing, IPv6 FakeIP, Google/AI/PT/Microsoft/GameDownload/Private rule providers and routes, and removed the sample airport subscription placeholder.
- Corrected MosDNS FakeIP upstream defaults and tag normalization for `nocnfake` / `cnfake`.
- Added a MosDNS upstream DNS add/edit dialog and group-level enable toggles while preserving raw upstream server fields on save.
- Fixed MosDNS system setting switch mappings.
- Fixed MosDNS client scan reset so `mosdns_client_ips` and `client_ip.txt` are cleared together.
</Changes>
</Plugin>
