<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Plugin>
<Name>msf</Name>
<PluginURL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/scoltzero/msf/main/msf.plg</PluginURL>
<Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/scoltzero/msf/main/packaging/unraid/msf.png</Icon>
<Overview>
A free and open-source, user-facing all-in-one management tool for DNS and proxy (mihomo / sing-box, in development), packaged for Unraid.
msf installs a lightweight Settings control page plus a self-managed local service. The Settings page is only for enabling the rc service, setting the listen host/port, choosing the data directory, viewing status, and opening the separate msf WebUI. The full DNS/proxy management interface runs in that WebUI.
After you complete the in-app setup wizard, msf can run MosDNS (DNS), Mihomo (proxy/TProxy), and the required nftables rules. Online MosDNS/Mihomo/Zashboard core downloads are verified against GitHub Release API asset SHA-256 digests before install; local uploads remain user-supplied files and are not marked as project-verified. Default sample subscriptions/nodes are inert placeholders only. Persistent data lives under /mnt/user/appdata/msf.
Update and remove msf from the Unraid Plugins page (not via the in-app updater).
</Overview>
<Support>https://github.com/scoltzero/msf/issues</Support>
<Project>https://github.com/scoltzero/msf</Project>
<Category>Network:Management Tools:System Plugins:</Category>
<Beta>False</Beta>
<Date>2026-06-17</Date>
<Changes>
### msf 0.3.5
- Fixed `msf update` so Linux tarball/systemd updates preserve the installed data directory and no longer make the WebUI look reset after update.
- `msf update` now reuses the installed host/port unless explicitly overridden and continues to direct Docker, Unraid, and fnOS FPK installs to platform managers.
- The WebUI Update Status card now shows a spinning state icon, process bar, dynamic progress, and recent logs during check/download/install/restart/failure phases.
- Self-update APIs now expose `phase`, `message`, and `events`, with backend logs for connecting, downloading, installing, restarting, and failed states.
- Default Mihomo configs now include MetaCubeX `geox-url`, and msf auto-provisions GeoSite/GeoIP data files for generated non-custom configs.
- Mihomo provider health checks now use `http://detectportal.firefox.com/success.txt` to reduce false negatives on restricted networks.
</Changes>
</Plugin>
